<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Zion Sheng</title>
    <link>https://zs144.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Zion Sheng</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://zs144.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>PinFuse: Diffusion-Aware Denoising for Spatial Transcriptomics [Ongoing]</title>
      <link>https://zs144.github.io/research/project-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zs144.github.io/research/project-four/</guid>
      <description>PinFuse reduces diffusion-induced noise in spatial transcriptomics data, allowing users to recover higher-fidelity gene expression signals and achieve more accurate downstream analyses.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SemiSeg: A Novel Graph-based Cell Typing Algorithm for Subcellular High-resolution Spatial Transcriptomics Data [Ongoing]</title>
      <link>https://zs144.github.io/research/project-three/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zs144.github.io/research/project-three/</guid>
      <description>Developed a new method that incorporates cell boundary constraints to guide neighbor-aware cell typing, resulting in more accurate single-cell gene expression profiles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention-based Multiple Instance Learning of Head and Neck Cancer Grading on Digital Pathology Using Vision-language Foundation Models</title>
      <link>https://zs144.github.io/research/project-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zs144.github.io/research/project-two/</guid>
      <description>Adapted Vision-Language Foundational Models (VLFM) to perform interpretable HNSCC tumor grading on H&amp;amp;E whole slide images (WSI) via attention-based multiple instance learning.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Self-Supervised Pre-training on Satellite Imagery Better than ImageNet? A Systematic Study with Sentinel-2</title>
      <link>https://zs144.github.io/research/project-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Feb 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zs144.github.io/research/project-one/</guid>
      <description>Systematically evaluated self-supervised pre-training on in-domain versus out-of-domain foundational datasets for downstream tasks in satellite imagery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zion Sheng - Resume</title>
      <link>https://zs144.github.io/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zs144.github.io/resume/</guid>
      <description>Resume Content This file contains the structured data for your BelResume template. The actual layout and styling is handled by the custom layout template.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
